# Vladimir Dobrovolskyy

Full stack web developer (Python/Django + Vue.js)

dobrovolskyy.vladimir@gmail.com skype: vladimir\_acc@outlook.com

web: vladimir.cc.ua

### **PROFILE**

Experienced Full-stack web developer with a background in digital marketing. Knowledgeable in all stages of product creation: from idea to launch and beyond. Able to understand what the client needs from a marketing standpoint and how to do it from a developer's.

# **EXPERIENCE**

## FREELANCE FULL-STACK WEB DEVELOPER — 2018 - PRESENT

- Planned, developed, tested, deployed, and maintained web applications built using the Django framework. Current main project is a publisher's site with 14k users.
- Translated client ideas into web application designs and systems.
- Participated in market research, had direct conversations with end-users and found ways to make main product's features on par or better than competitor's.

# PRODUCT MANAGER AT JSC BLITZ-INFORM, KYIV — 2016 - 2018

- Wrote product strategy and managed the development by a team of 3.
- Was researching tools and frameworks offered by devs to clarify that they fit our end goals at first and then to set tasks as precisely as possible.
- Started coding to speed things up and ensure my team can work on core tasks without distractions.

# MARKETING MANAGER AT JSC BLITZ-INFORM, KYIV — 2014 – 2016

Single-handedly built digital marketing from scratch: refreshed old site's design, added user registration, integrated email marketing service (forms, triggers, mail templates, etc.), made technical SEO, and started social media accounts.

Gathered analytics data and feedback from staff and customers about current digital products to form requirements for future ones.

# **EDUCATION**

Kyiv national university of trade and economics (KNUTE), Master of Marketing — 2013

### SKILLS

Python	Django (+ REST framework)	Digital Marketing & analytics	Git
Vue.js	HTML&CSS	Product roadmap & strategy	UI/UX
Docker	Project management	Team leading	Figma